Celebrity Roast are some of the highest
rated programs on Comedy Central but I
think they might be running out of
people to roast I mean they offer me a
spot on the day of this new one I'm not
proud of it but I still did it it's the
Comedy Central roast of a baby featuring
roast Master General Jeff Ross anyway
baby I'm not going to say you're ugly
but Angelina Jolie got to look at you
and said H Eight is
Enough Hannibal burus nice hair baby
does your Barbie use scissors or
chemotherapy Eddie peppone you were just
in your mom's stomach for n months must
have been nice all warm and cozy
swimming around in my
jiz L baby of course got into a little
trouble when she was call on tape saying
the n word and I'm not mad at you but it
was your first word International
Superstar
Charro what it worki show me the way to
the bu you say what the hell I'm going
to do with a little bit Gucci Gucci un
roasted and special guest the baby mama
you're going to be sucking on these tits
later not you baby the two black guys
next to
you when your parents change their
diapers they keep the and throw you away
baby where the single mom's in the house
tonight guess you lost the baby weight
to
AIDS you you cry when you tired you cry
when you hungry are you a baby or an
I considered getting an abortion
because Planned Parenthood offered me
$30 for your
liver no one loves you baby you were
found next to a dumpster because the
dumpster gave you
up you're so stupid you actually were
born
yesterday baby's like why am I getting
roasted by this Uber
driver
baby you have a face only a mother can
love which sucks because I don't love
you take that infant comedy Central's
roast of a baby sponsored by sunlasses
[Music]
why